MITSUKI MIYAGI

Full Stack Developer

**** +8131**-339-**0238

github.com/mitsukimiyagi39

- @ miyagimitsuki39@gmail.com
- Misatocho, JP



SUMMARY

Senior full stack developer with 5+ years of experience designing and building responsive web design. Proficient with CSS and JS Frameworks, with extensive knowledge of UX and user psychology. Notable achievements include boosting the conversion rate of an existing website by 80% with improved code and design.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Fullstack Developer

Chetu

iii 2021.05 - 2023.03 ♀ Florida

- Started building features and fixing bugs in an existing codebase from the first day after knowledge transfer.
- Created a library that abstracts away the complexities of end-to-end tests and started integrating end-to-end tests into the project.
- Developed new React hooks to reduce the amount of duplicated code in the codebase.
- Established and maintained a Go API with a PostgreSQL database.

Backend Developer

OPTIM

- Developed a back-end service for multiplayer games with video calling capability between players.
- Reconfigured the Socket.IO connection so that the server still recognizes registered clients, even after a server crash.
- Integrated a Cloud Firestore database with an existing codebase.
- Refactored an existing codebase for a multiplayer gaming platform and decoupled and modularized the code.

Frontend Developer

GMO Internet Group

苗 2019.02 - 2019.11 🗣 Tokyo, JP

- Scraped production-level websites to replicate them locally and performed updates on them.
- Implemented CSS changes on the fly, using the browser only where code was not convenient for use.
- · Adapted styles to a variety of screen sizes and different browser environments.

EDUCATION

Computer Science

University of Miyazaki

2013 - 2017

LANGUAGES

English

Fluent



SKILLS

Design mockups and wireframes

Building APIs

ReactJS Next.JS Responsive Design

JavaScript TypeScript PostgreSQL

Cypress Laravel PHP

TRAINING / COURSES

International Business

Entrepreneurship & Innovation

Leadership

STRENGTHS



Up-to-Date Technology

To love learning new technology is force of my progressive.



Perfect Result

It is important for me to do perfect. In any case, I want to do with my strength, perfectly.